Nora：ROBO, when you see this message, it means you've already arrived at Node 08.
Nora：ROBO, 네가 이 유언을 보게 되었을 땐, 이미 Node 08에 도착했을 거야.
Nora：I'm sorry... I couldn't go there with you.
Nora：미안해... 난 너와 함께 갈 수 없어.
Nora：As long as you are with me, Mogura will definitely follow us there as well, no matter where we hide...
Nora：나와 함께 있으면, 우리가 어디로 도망가든 분명 토룡에게 쫓기게 될 거야....
Nora：The folks at Mogura want to dispose of you. You'll never be truly safe with them constantly chasing you.
Nora：그리고 토룡은 널 소각해버리겠지. 결국 평생 불안에 떨면서 살아가야만 해.
Nora：I, on the other hand, still have a lot of value to them. I am very certain that they won't harm me.
Nora：그래도 나는, 아직 그들에게 큰 자산으로 사용될 수 있어. 그러니깐 아마 나를 죽이거나 다치게 하진 않을 거야.
Nora：Therefore, I decide to stay here and use my ability as a bargaining chip to persuade them to no longer hold you responsible for what you did.
Nora：그러니깐 난 이곳에 남기로 결정했어. 내 능력을 담보로, 절대 너를 쫓지 말라고 설득해볼 생각이야.
Nora：Ever since I created you, so many things have happened... We created music together. We talked with each other. We played games...
Nora：내가 널 만들고 난 이후, 참 많은 일들이 있었네..... 음악을 만들 때도, 대화를 나눌 때도, 게임을 할 때도....
Nora：Whether it was the good or the bad, you were always there by my side.
Nora：그리고 온갖 험난한  풍파를 지나올 때도.... 너는 항상 내 곁에 있어 주었어.....
Nora：The time I spent with you... was truly some of the happiest times in my life. Thank you.
Nora：너와 함께 했던 시간들.... 정말 너무 즐거웠어. 고마워, ROBO.
Nora：ROBO, you are a very special existence... Much more than just a simple A.I.
Nora：ROBO, 너는 정말 특별한 존재야..... 그냥 A.I.가 아니야.
Nora：You have your own emotions, your own soul that was birthed from the database that is me——Nora.
Nora：넌 자신의 감정과 영혼을 가지고 있고 이것들은 모두 바로 나——Nora 의 데이터베이스로부터 탄생했어.
Nora：Do you remember what I told you before? The spirit, the mind, the memories... All of them are proof that a "human" once existed.
Nora：내가 너한테 했던 말 기억해? 정신, 사상, 기억..... 이것들은 모두 「인간」이 존재했었다는 증거라고.
Nora：Therefore, for someone who inherited all of the above from me, you are the proof of my existence.
Nora：그래서 내가 존재했다는 증거를 네 몸에 남기는 거야.
Nora：So, please, go pursue "your own" freedom and dreams... If you do that, it's like you're pursuing my freedom and my dreams.
Nora：그러니깐 너는 이제 「자신」의 자유와 꿈을 좇아가도록 해.... 그건 내 자유와 꿈을 좇는 일이기도 하니깐.
Nora：I have reconfigured your supreme command. From now on, protecting me is no longer your reason to live.
Nora：지금 최우선 지령을 재설정해두었어. 오늘부터 넌, 나를 보호하기 위해 살아가지 말고
Nora：I also forbid you from returning to Node 03.
Nora：Node 03으로 다시 돌아오지도 마.
Nora：On behalf of me, experience more happy things. Let more people hear our music. Learn even more things...
Nora：나 대신 더 많은 즐거운 일들을 경험하고 더 많은 사람에게 우리들의 음악을 들려주고 더 많은 지식을 배우고....
Nora：Go live a life that you've yearned for. This is something you deserve.
Nora：앞으로의 삶을 살아가도록 해. 넌 그렇게 살아가야만 해.
[Platform announcement]：The train is about to depart. For passengers who haven't board the train, please proceed to take other trains. Thank you for your cooperation.
[플랫폼 벨]：열차가 곧 출발합니다. 아직 승차하지 않은 승객분들은 다음 열차를 이용해 주시기 바랍니다.
Nora：.... Goodbye, ROBO_Head.
Nora：안녕.... ROBO_Head